907 Forest Drive, Garner, NC 27529 (919) 921-7562 massengillashley@icloud.com ashleymassengill.github.io

ashlevmassengill.com

OVERVIEW

Through my experiences, I have learned where my strengths lie. I enjoy writing code and turning designs into interactive products through HTML and CSS. My goal is to continue growing my experience and knowledge in ways that allow me to tap into the creative and organized sides of my personality to create a product that is the best outcome for everyone.

STRENGTHS

- ★ Creative Thinking
- ★ Great Eye for Detail
- ★ Analytical Thinking

- ★ Extreme Efficiency
- ★ Teaching Skills
- ★ Organization

PROJECT HISTORY

UI Designer & Developer, diaBEATthis

[i] Jan 2017

diaBEATthis is a website and web app focused on assisting diabetes suferers track and manage the various aspects of their disease.

 Visual Design
Style Guide
Branding
Page Layouts
Front End Code Tech: Illustrator, Photoshop, Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, Skeleton, jQuery, Github

UI Developer, Treasures Unearthed

[i] Nov 2016

Treasures Unearthed is a virtual exhibit of the North Carolina Museum of Natural Science

 Visual Design
Navigation
Content
Interactive Map Tech: Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, Skeleton, jQuery, GitHub

UI Designer & Developer, Goodreads Bookshelf Redesign © Nov 2016 Goodreads is an Amazon owned personal reading list management site. with a dated and confusing design, needing a complete overhaul.

• Visual Design • Rebranding • Content • Page Layouts • Front End Code Tech: Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, jQuery, GitHub, Illustrator

WORK HISTORY

Database Manager, RCI, Inc.

i Apr 2016 - Jul 2016

(\$) Raleigh, NC

- Managed internal tech support including computer hardware, software, phone systems, servers, and website.
- Guided implementation of new AMS through search, demon, contract, setup and testing phases into training and go-live.
- Created and maintained all reporting operations for each department.

Meetings Specialist, RCI, Inc.

i Dec 2010 - Apr 2016

Raleigh, NC

- Produced event based website layouts and coding.
- Managed all event registrations for 10+ attendee events to 1500+ attedee events.
- Created all meeting collateral for international events from general education to conventions and trade shows.

Customer Relations Manager,

i Aug 2007 - Mar 2010

\$ Raleigh, NC

North Carolina Chamber

- Database management, including ensuring data accuracy.
- Internal IT support in collaboration with external IT team.
- Processed all event registrations and assisted in minor logistics.
- Created and maintained all company-wide reporting processes and data analytics.

TECHNOLOGIES

HTMI 5 CSS3

SASS

iQuery

Atom

Skeleton

Bootstrap

GitHub

Windows

iTerm

Mac OS

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe InDesign

Microsoft Office Trello

Apple iWork

Adobe Acrobat

Google Docs

Crystal Reports

EDUCATION

UI Design, The Iron Yard

i Oct 2016 - Jan 2017

(\$) Raleigh, NC

East Carolina University

i Aug 2001 - May 2003

(\$) Greenville, NC

VOLUNTEER HISTORY

Guest Services NC State Athletics

🗓 Aug 2016 - current

\$ Raleigh, NC

Box Office & Boutique Assistant Carolina Ballet

🗓 Aug 2010 - current

\$ Raleigh, NC

Admissions & Ticketing Services USGA Men's & Women's US Open

[i] Jul 2014

(\$) Pinehurst, NC

Event Assistant SPARKcon

Sept 2009

\$ Raleigh, NC

AFFILIATIONS

AIGA Raleigh

Triangle UXPA

INTERESTS















